Guidline

This website contains the following contents:
- new page
- designers view
- products view
- contact

following functions:
- view designers by scrolling up/down the mouse
- view products by scrolling up/down (left/right) the mouse
- mouse hover product img, show contents on larger screen (>2k), less than 2K, the title disappear
- mouse hover the main page center, turn on the speaker, there are heart beats
- click login to login (Run the createDatabase.php first. Make sure XAMPP is turned on)
- click 登出（log out） on the bottom to log out

*****One page is not finished due to the lack of contents by the company. They ask to put a coming soon there

Implementations
- animation implemented in Jquery and JS
- Login function implemented by JS and PHP and Mysql
- CSS styled
- used Session variables to store the state of first/Login.
- cookie check via PHP and JS




