What did you change/enhance from part 1?
-Enhanced the whole UI design of the website and animation. 
-Also added the fully functioning login. Registration is not added due to time limit. 
-Also fixed the animation queue bug.
-complete all other pages. One page called 介绍 is still coming soon because the company has not provide me with the info yet.

If there was a third part to the class project, what would you like to implement?
-I will complete the registration page
-I will upload it to a real server, make it online (although I am doing it privately after class since it is my business :))
-make the UI and animation even more nicer and smoother
-add the online business request page with the form submitting functioning, send to the company email.
-make it more responsive.
-add a google map or any China map service connect to the map under contact us.联系我们. So when click the map will direct the site to a map web App, and locate

What did you learn between part 1 and part 2?
-the use of Javascript.Jquery 
-how does the php session work. Fully understood.
-Web UI design skill improved. Understood the Css attributes much more while doing the project. My next project should look better.

What did you like about this project? How could it have been better?
-it is totally free! I like the free way to do work
-improved my skill a lot
-if you could make it harder and require more challenging stuff at the begining next time, that would be great.


Overall. Great project!
Hope I will get an A over this course :)
Thanks! Matt




Ziyao